A Guide to the Ruiz Case Office of Special Master Records, 1979-1992.
Ruiz Case Office of Special Master Records,
- Defendants first semi-annual report on section III of the stipulation moidifying crowding provisions of the amended decrees, Vols. I II (Box 94-458/30 (05274659))
- TDC, psychiatric services plan, February 1984 (Box 94-458/31 (05268157))
- Special masters report concerning adequacy of defendants' mentally retarded offender plan, filed December 1, 1984 (Box 94-458/31 (05268157))
- Special masters report, 24th monitors report, OSHA plan, defendants compliance with TDC plan of October 21, 1982 (Box 94-458/31 (05268157))
- OSHA report of monitor and Special Master and addendum (Box 94-458/31 (05268157))
- Fire safety orders (Box 94-458/31 (05268157))
- TDC compliance reports, area of environmental health and safety (Box 94-458/31 (05268157))
- 24th monitors report, OSHA (Box 94-458/31 (05268157))
- Special master's report concerning the 24th monitors report, OSHA with addendum (Box 94-458/31 (05268157))
- Miscellaneous papers (Box 94-458/32 (05274910))
- Correspondence to: (Box 94-458/32 (05274910))
  - William Justice (Box 94-458/32 (05274910))
  - D. Gunther (Box 94-458/32 (05274910))
  - Prisoners (Box 94-458/32 (05274910))
- William Wayne Justice correspondence, 2.0 (Box 94-458/33 (05268102))
- William Wayne Justice correspondence, 2.1 (Box 94-458/33 (05268102))
- Correspondence to Daniel Gunther (Box 94-458/33 (05268102))
- Vincet Nathan, Special Master (Box 94-458/33 (05268102))
- Houston trip (Box 94-458/33 (05268102))
- Ruiz miscellaneous (Box 94-458/33 (05268102))
- Temporary law clerk (Box 94-458/33 (05268102))
- Texas Board of Corrections correspondence (Box 94-458/33 (05268102))
- Special Master's reports, 68th-76th (Box 94-458/34 (05268190))
- Prisoner correspondence (Box 94-458/35 (05274976))
- Monitor's reports, 6th-12th (Box 94-458/36 (05268179))
- Harvey vs. Estelle (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Roberson vs. Williams (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Hart vs. TDC (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Harvey vs. Estell, et. al. (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Dillion vs. Estelle (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Harvey vs. Ferguson, et. al. (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Henderson vs. Estelle (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Ansley vs. Wade (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Gabel vs. Estelle (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Wagner vs. Heard, et. al. (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Smith vs. Mrs. Deutt (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Bennett vs. Estelle (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Lockhart vs. Estelle (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Brown vs. Estelle (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Ewing vs. Estelle, et. al. (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Florio, John T. (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Soriano, vs. Estelle (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Denby vs. Heard (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Nieto vs. Estelle (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Holguin vs. Estelle (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Morales vs. Estelle (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Fairley vs. Estelle (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Yarborough vs. Lauper (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Sanner vs. Burgess (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Christian, Lorenzo D. (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Aranda vs. Estelle (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Connolly vs. Springer (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Mudd, Robert Lee (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Blaylock vs. Estelle (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Guerra vs. Estelle (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Penby vs. Shoemaker (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Pendergras vs. Jack A. (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Fuller vs. Estelle (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Price vs. Warden Savage (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Brown vs. Sanchez (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Caraway vs. APD (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Jackson vs. Estelle (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Derry vs. Estelle (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Hay vs. Jack A. (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- McClain vs. Estelle (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Austin vs. Brown, et. al. (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Becknell vs. Anderson (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Jiminez vs. Estelle (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Aranda vs. Estelle (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Franks, Hershel (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Surgers vs. Atchison (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- McShan vs. Estelle (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Yarborough vs. Ware (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Frank vs. Stauber (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Page vs. Estelle (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Knight vs. Caldwell (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Mudd, Robert (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Bradford vs. Wardens (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Reed vs. Hardy (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Bynum vs. Estelle (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Blaylock vs. Estelle (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Rumph vs. Jacko (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Johnson vs. Estelle (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Fuller and Eubanks vs. Estelle, et. al. (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Waddington vs. Myers, et. al. (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Wilbert Williams (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Hollis vs. Estelle (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Stiehl vs. White (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Barber vs. Estelle (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Numley vs. Estelle (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Boyd vs. Estelle (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Tuberville vs. Estelle (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Walker vs. Lawson and Woods (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Warren vs. Sutton and Losack (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Uresti vs. Estelle (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Roberts vs. Estelle, et. al. (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Aranda vs. Estelle (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Johnson vs. Estelle (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Bailey vs. Estelle (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Green vs. Procunier (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Moses vs. Bidwell (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Daniels vs. Estelle, et. al. (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Spears vs. Jones (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Long vs. Gray (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Dosier vs. Estelle, et. al. (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Zuniga vs. Boone, et. al. (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Patton vs. Mabry, et. al. (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Mitchell vs. Drewery, et. al. (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Aldridge vs. McKaskle, et. al. (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Waffer vs. Rodriguez, et. al. (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Martinez vs. Waldron, et. al. (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Mikel vs. Jiminez, et. al. (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Rena, Juan R. (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Beauduy vs. Lennon (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Milligan vs. Estelle, et. al. (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Johnson vs. Beale (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Franks vs. Hardy (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Williams vs. parker (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Jones vs. Anderson (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Ackerman, Albert (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Green vs. Woods, et. al. (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Davidson vs. Dawson (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- McDaniel vs. Grivich (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Campbell vs. Beia (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Brewer vs. Procuier, et. al. (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Briggs vs. Copeland, et. al. (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Henderson vs. McKaskle, et. al. (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Eubanks vs. Sanders (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Kring, Clarence J. (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Norsworthy vs. Mckaskle (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Hollis, William Byron (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Mikel, Buddy (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Money vs. Estelle (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Hall, Robert A. (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Hay vs. Noya, et. al. (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Scheneck vs. McKaskle (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Becknell, James (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Thomas vs. Estelle, et. al. (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Randolph vs. Estelle (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Williams, Dalton (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Dunlap vs. Weaver (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Sams, Gary W. (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Delgado, Robert (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Jones vs. Treon (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Czapala, Patrick M. (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Jones vs. Lawson (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Robinson vs. Austin (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Rollins vs. Woods (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Duncan, Alvin C. (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Cay, Kevin M. (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Eubanks, Wesley (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Jones vs. Hodges, et. al. (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Manning vs. Hodges, et. al. (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Valles vs. Estelle, et. al. (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Lewis, Billy L. (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Stewart vs. Calfee (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Tone vs. McKaskle, et. al. (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Hickson vs. Mckaskle, et. al. (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Martin vs. McElvancy (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Murphy vs. McKaskle (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Harrelson vs. Procunier (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Hagans vs. McKaskle (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Seifullah aka J. Powell (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Seifullah aka James Lee (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- martinez, Mario (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Cramer, Granville (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Adams, Robert C. (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Bankhead, James X. (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Blalock, James E. (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Arnold, Pete (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Calvin, Denny L. (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Moreno, Ralph (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Tisdale, Ronnie W. (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Becknell, James B. (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Newman, Ernest Dale (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Patterson, Joe Bob (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Smith vs. Strains, et. al. (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Hay, Herbert D. (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Rose, Eddie Ray (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Walls vs. Gunn, et. al. (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Hendrickson, D. (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Perez, Guadalupe (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Short, Kenneth (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Adams, David L. (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- A. Ansley (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Lee, Wendell A. (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Walls vs. Procunier (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Ashe, Billy J. (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Simmons vs. Procunier (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Arnold, Pete (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Walls vs. Procunier, et. al. (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Briggs, Preston (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Davis, Bobby J. (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Turner, Robert (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Brown, Leon (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Burrell, Clyde J. (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Jackson, Samuel J. (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Sierra, Bernardino (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Thomas, Preston A. (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- McCullough, Edward (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Houff, Olie (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Sawyer, David R. (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Ladd vs. Fry (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Wendt, Harvey (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Rahman, Malika (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Ross, Raymond (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Ugdan, Mushin H. (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Kiser, Bobby D. (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Plazinichdums (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Williams, Floyd E. (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Gordon vs. State of Texas, et. al. (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Starkey, Terry (Box 94-458/37 (05274626))
- Early Ruiz (Box 94-458/38 (05274648))
- Inmate affidavits (Box 94-458/38 (05274648))
- Corrections Magazine, March 1978 (Box 94-458/38 (05274648))
- TDC, special needs plan, August 11, 1981 (Box 94-458/38 (05274648))
- Report and recommendations concerning the status of Huntsville Unit Hospital, August 19, 1981 (Box 94-458/38 (05274648))
- Plan for the development of new or alternative housing for inmates in need of chronic care or acute psychological and psychiatric care, September 1, 1981 (Box 94-458/38 (05274648))
- Motions and affidavits, May 16, 1983 (Box 94-458/38 (05274648))
- Defendants alternative hospital plan, August 20, 1981 (Box 94-458/38 (05274648))
- Defendants housing plan, August 5, 1981 (Box 94-458/38 (05274648))
- Housing report, November 1981 (Box 94-458/38 (05274648))
- US response to the defendants special needs, Mental health plan, November 9, 1981 (Box 94-458/38 (05274648))
- Notice of deposition, November 19, 1981 (Box 94-458/38 (05274648))
- Reports of contact (Box 94-458/38 (05274648))
- Administrative segregation plan, April 20, 1981 (Box 94-458/38 (05274648))
- Record of proceedings, oral hearing on plaintiffs' motion for further prelininary relief and defendants' motion for preliminary relief, July 15-16, 1976 (Box 94-458/38 (05274648))
- Record of proceedings, testimony of Martin H. Gerry, April 19-20, 23, 1979 (Box 94-458/38 (05274648))
- Post trial memorandum, Vol. I II (Box 94-458/38 (05274648))
- Post trial reply memorandum, February 22, 1980 (Box 94-458/38 (05274648))
- Post trial brief for plaintiffs (Box 94-458/38 (05274648))
- Memorandum opinion, December 12, 1980 (Box 94-458/38 (05274648))
- VHS video, TDC agreement, TDC crisis, April-May, 1982 (Box 94-458/38 (05274648))
- Prisoner correspondence, January-August, 1992 (Box 94-458/39 (05274637))
- Memorandum from Governor Clements to William Bennett Turner (Box 94-458/39 (05274637))
- Alberti case concerning William P. Clements, et. al. (Box 94-458/39 (05274637))
- Report to the office of the Special Master pursuant to the stipulation concerning order of April 24, 1987 (Box 94-458/39 (05274637))
- termination of the Mastership (Box 94-458/39 (05274637))
- Classification plan (Box 94-458/39 (05274637))
- Defendants trusty camp assesment and motion to find defendants in contempt and for further relief with appendicies (Box 94-458/39 (05274637))
- Refer to Special Master, OCtober 1984 (Box 94-458/40 (05274615))
- Special Master referral orders entered on prisoner pleadings, December 1984 (Box 94-458/40 (05274615))
- January 1985 (Box 94-458/40 (05274615))
- Severance orders signed (Box 94-458/40 (05274615))
- Standing orders, signed (Box 94-458/40 (05274615))
- Refer to Special Master, January 1985 (Box 94-458/40 (05274615))
- Severance orders entered, January 1985 (Box 94-458/40 (05274615))
- Prisoner pleadings severed (Box 94-458/40 (05274615))
- Severance orders entered, February 1985 (Box 94-458/40 (05274615))
- Prisoner pleadings, preferred to master's office, March 1985 (Box 94-458/40 (05274615))
- Prisoner pleadings, severed, Eastern District of Texas, March 1985 (Box 94-458/40 (05274615))
- Sent to Special Master, April 1985 (Box 94-458/40 (05274615))
- Severed to Eastern District, April 1985 (Box 94-458/40 (05274615))
- Severed to Southern district, April 1985 (Box 94-458/40 (05274615))
- Severed, Western District (Box 94-458/40 (05274615))
- Severed to Southern District, May 1985 (Box 94-458/40 (05274615))
- Severed to Eastern district, May 1985 (Box 94-458/40 (05274615))
- Sent to Special Master, May 1985 (Box 94-458/40 (05274615))
- TDC Safety Manual, 1985 (Box 94-458/41 (05274921))
- Prison financing and construction plan, July 1987 (Box 94-458/41 (05274921))
- 41st monitors report, report on the state of defendants' compliance at the Darlington Unit … (Box 94-458/41 (05274921))
- Report concerning 41st report (Box 94-458/41 (05274921))
- Report concerning 39th report (Box 94-458/41 (05274921))
- Defendants report on compliance with administrative segregation conditions and violence (Box 94-458/41 (05274921))
- Report of the 38th report (Box 94-458/41 (05274921))
- 39th monitors report, report on the state of defendants compliance at the Eastham Unit …, 1986 (Box 94-458/41 (05274921))
- 38th monitors report, report on sections IV.A and IV.B of the amended decree granting equitable relief and declaratory judgement …, January 23, 1987 (Box 94-458/41 (05274921))
- Appendices to 39th report (Box 94-458/41 (05274921))
- TDC, Occupational Safety and Health Manual, July 1983 (Box 94-458/41 (05274921))
- 36th monitors report, report on the state of defendants' compliance with section VI of the stipulation modifying crowding provisions of amended decree (Box 94-458/41 (05274921))
- Report concerning 31st report (Box 94-458/41 (05274921))
- 31st monitors report, report on section III of the consent decree (Box 94-458/41 (05274921))
- Report concerning 36th report (Box 94-458/41 (05274921))
- 19th quarterly compliance report, June 1987 (Box 94-458/41 (05274921))
- 8th quarterly compliance report (Box 94-458/41 (05274921))
- Semi-annual progress report on TDCs comprehensive health care plan, psychiatric services plan, mentally retarded offender plan, physically handicapped, October 1986 - March 1987 (Box 94-458/41 (05274921))
- 15th quarterly compliance report, June 1986 (Box 94-458/41 (05274921))
- 4th quarterly compliance report, June 1986 (Box 94-458/41 (05274921))
- 1st quarterly compliance report, September 1985 (Box 94-458/41 (05274921))
- Ruiz vs. L. O. McCotter, September 1985 (Box 94-458/41 (05274921))
- Health Care Plan, 1984 (Box 94-458/41 (05274921))
- TDC Classification Plan, 1984 (Box 94-458/41 (05274921))
- TDC, dental services, needs and staffing requirements, 1986 (Box 94-458/41 (05274921))
- Guajardo vs. Estelle (Box 94-458/41 (05274921))
- Report on 32nd report (Box 94-458/41 (05274921))
- TDC health services division, policies and procedures manual, December 1984 (Box 94-458/41 (05274921))
- Davis vs. Procunier (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
- Haas, Chester V. (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
- Davis vs. Jiminez (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
- Buchanan vs. Durbin (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
- M. Williams (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
- Harvey L. Wendt (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
- Ansley vs. Reese (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
- Uquah vs. Munden (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
- Rogers vs. Procunier (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
- Danny R. Watts (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
- David G. Shockley (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
- Mark C. Calhoun (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
- Harry Green (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
- Robert Williams (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
- B. R. Hendrix (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
- David Southworth (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
- Southworth vs. Baker, et. al. (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
- Hendrix vs. McElaney (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
- marvin McLure (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
- Albert Lee White (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
- Otis Lee Fairly (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
- jacinto Nevares (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
- David J. Adams (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
- Ronnie Massengill (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
- Dallas Hunter (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
- John H. Money, Jr. (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
- Mark H. Kolbert (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
- William B. Hollis (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
- Alfred F. Garcia (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
- Levi Guzman (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
- Johnny Bailey (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
- Paul Garivay (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
- Carl M. Brown (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
- James William Smith (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
- Forte V. Thomas (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
- Earl T. Bratcher (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
- Incarcerated citizens vs. McCotter, Director TDC (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
- David W. Burton (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
- Benigno Pena (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
- Noffie Johnson (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
- Cleveland Hawkins (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
- David L. Adams (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
- Lufkin Division: (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
  - De La Cerna vs. West (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
  - Sanders vs. Holland (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
  - Boyer and Sheppard vs. Jones (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
  - Hall vs. Warden Turner (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
  - Johnson vs. Sheriff's Department, Houston County, Texas (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
  - Johnson vs. Sims (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
  - Reed vs. Estelle, et. al. (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
  - Jordan vs. Estelle, et. al. (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
  - Smith vs. Estelle, et. al. (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
  - Ramirez vs. Estelle, et. al. (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
  - Johnson vs. Welch (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
  - Moore vs. Ramirez, et. al. (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
  - Rose vs. Ross, et. al. (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
  - Holts vs. Estelle (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
  - Davis vs. Clements (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
  - Youngblood vs. Estelle (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
  - Reed vs. Estelle, Jr. (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
  - Rolling vs. Torres, et. al. (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
  - Holts vs. Ware (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
  - De La Cerna vs. Clements (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
  - Brown vs. Texas Board of Pardons and Paroles (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
  - Bayes vs. Clements (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
  - Carey vs. Texas Board of Pardons and Paroles (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
  - Haas vs. Estelle (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
  - Hall vs. Turner (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
  - Shoots vs. Estelle (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
  - Moore vs. McClothen (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
  - Turner vs. Estelle (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
  - Degrate vs. Billings (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
  - Moore vs. Estelle (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
  - Moore vs. William Patti (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
  - Smith vs. Estelle, et. al. (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
  - Gordon vs. Estelle, Jr., et. al. (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
  - Appleman vs. Lightfoot (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
  - Townsend vs. Estelle (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
  - Thompson vs. Frizzell (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
  - Moore vs. Stephens (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
  - King vs. Estelle, et. al. (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
  - Holts vs. Turner (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
  - Moore vs. Jiminez (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
  - Cooper vs. Turner (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
  - Guy vs. Dr. Bul (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
  - Alaniz vs. Torres (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
  - Pierce vs. Estelle (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
  - Bradford vs. Estelle (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
  - Carter vs. Estelle (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
  - Evans vs. Estelle (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
  - Shoots vs. Estelle (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
  - Richardson, Willie D. (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
  - Weare vs. Estelle (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
  - Walker vs. Torres (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
  - Powers vs. Phillips and Demory (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
  - Cortes and Menefee vs. Turner (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
  - Weare vs. Estelle (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
  - Killingsworth vs. Dr. Bul (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
  - Evans vs. Goodwin (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
  - Boyd vs. Estelle (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
  - Eaton vs. Estelle (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
  - Hall vs. Estelle (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
  - Gordon vs. Estelle and Turner (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
  - George vs. Maples (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
  - Benton vs. Nacogdoches (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
  - Carr vs. Falasoski, et. al. (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
  - Smith vs. Estelle (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
  - Rose vs. Walker (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
  - Hall and Crow vs. Johnson (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
  - McGuire vs. Turner (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
  - Shears vs. Lightfoot (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
  - McGuire vs. Roseberry (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
  - Kingsbury, Ervin E. (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
  - Johnson, Charles E. (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
  - Williams vs. Estelle (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
  - Smith vs. Estelle (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
  - Jones vs. Torres, et. al. (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
  - Smith vs. Estelle, et. al. (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
  - Kingsbury vs. Estelle, et. al. (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
  - Hamilton, Eudell and Donna vs. Estelle (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
  - Baltimore vs. Estelle, et. al. (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
  - George vs. Estelle, et. al. (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
  - Ward vs. Estelle, et. al. (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
  - Calhoun vs. Cochran (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
  - Davis vs. Estelle (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
  - Thomas vs. Woods, et. al. (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
  - Shepperd vs. Estelle, et. al. (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
  - Rumph vs. Buck, et. al. (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
  - Rumph vs. Moore, et. al. (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
  - Karrah vs. Torres, et. al. (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
  - Bishop vs. Torres, et. al. (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
  - Sanford vs. Estelle (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))
  - Norman, Louis J. (Box 94-485/42 (05268113))